Damn that Krai...
It's the same excuse every time.
What the hell is going on?
Sven!
I wish I could help you, sir.
I've got a mountain of questions for him.
Obsidian Cross.
I believe you said you came
here to obtain a quest?
Correct.
You guys are trustworthy.
I'm sorry to spring this on you,
but could I ask you to
investigate the White Wolf's Den?
You really roped us in, didn't you?
Once again, we're all dancing
in the palm of your hand,
Krai.
We are now in the golden age
of the treasure hunters!
Amid the sparkling talent on
display in the capital of Zebrudia,
there was one man who stood
out amongst all others!
His name is Krai Andrey.
This is an epic tale
full of glory and agony,
of how he became renowned
for being the leader
of the strongest party he founded
with his childhood friends,
and also the master of the strongest clan!
Krai, this is the thing you
requested the other day.
Please take a look.
Thank you.
There's a lead on you-know-what, as well.
Oh!
Episode 06
I Want to Sleep Instead of Taking Charge
"I Want to Sleep Instead of Taking Charge."
Let This Grieving Soul Retire
Date! Date!
Today, I'm on another date with Krai!
Calm down, Liz.
We're not going on a date today.
This is the unsafest
neighborhood in the capital.
That's the S-Stifled Shadow.
What's she doing in a place like this?
So, do you have some kind of business
to take care of here, or what?
You could say that.
According to Eva's information,
one person after another has
gone missing in this area.
Not that disappearances are
super uncommon in the slum quarter,
but it would be really bad if
Sitri's Slime was attacking people.
Also...
it looks like there's a new
ice cream shop around here.
It's two birds with one stone.
It's really just like Eva to take
me seriously and look that up.
Krai?
Why don't we check out that
ice cream shop up ahead?
Yeah!
What are those two doing here?
I-Impossible...
How?
I was sure I wasn't being followed...
So letting me get away was a trap after all?
This can't be happening.
Nobody could know that this
newly opened ice cream shop is one
of our research facilities...
But still, Thousand Tricks is here...
At any rate, we're closing for the day!
Ow, ow, ow...
Are you all right?
I've returned.
Y-Y-Y-You're...
What's wrong?
You're back, Sophia?
We know you're in there!
Come on out!
How dare you...
Liz, please.
What?
They're closed today.
But I can smell something sweet, and
I'm pretty sure they were open a minute ago.
Hmm.
We shouldn't bother the
store owners, though.
Let's go home.
They probably ran out of ice cream.
I guess.
That was fruitless.
Because you didn't get to eat ice cream?
Huh? Yeah!
In the end, I couldn't find
Sitri's Slime anywhere.
I guess if a threat to the
capital were on the loose,
it wouldn't be this quiet...
But I really wonder where it is.
Liz?
When is Sitri getting back
from the Night Palace?
Si?
I could just do whatever you need done.
I need someone with knowledge
of magical organisms.
Oh, that.
Yeah, I guess she's the
only one who can help.
She took all kinds of equipment with her,
so I think she'll be a while.
I see.
It's fine.
She'll be back soon.
Right?
Excuse me.
Eva!
Hello!
Hello.
I've selected the members
who will aid the Association
in the investigation
of the White Wolf's Den.
Ark is not present,
but Sven and his group
have already gone ahead.
Thank you so much!
I'll let you handle it.
The investigation party will leave tomorrow.
An expert in relic research
will also be dispatched,
so it will be a very
thorough investigation.
This has become quite the thing.
Not that I'm going, so
it's none of my business.
Is there something of concern?
No, no, that sounds fine.
If it's members of Steps,
they'll do just fine.
Yup, yup.
Krai is right.
Then I will make the preparations.
That Thousand Tricks is
not to be trifled with.
I can't believe he found our facility
in the slums that easily...
That ice cream shop was a perfect front.
Does this mean his intelligence
network is better than ours?
And yet he just walked away!
He's incomprehensible!
There's no need to be frightened by pranks.
But how should we proceed while we are
uncertain of what Thousand Tricks is truly after?
What do you think, Sophia?
Let us fight.
We're up against a level 8!
Do we have any chance of winning?
Of course.
The Akashic Tower is in
pursuit of the truth.
The laws may not approve of our methods,
but there is no enemy we
need shy away from.
They are a group of high-level hunters.
This is the perfect opportunity to see how
effective the defense system I've built is.
If we eliminate them all,
we don't have to worry about our
information being compromised further.
What do you think?
Very well.
Since we've already been sniffed
out by Thousand Tricks,
there is no way for us to escape
completely unscathed.
We may as well rid ourselves
of them in one fell swoop.
Sophia, do as you wish.
Please let me take care of it,
Master.
Liz is really something.
I don't have a single bruise.
She must have soaked me in potions
and thrown me into bed after I fainted.
I'm glad I survived...
Why so many carriages?
What happened?
Tino.
You haven't heard?
We're going into the White Wolf's Den
in collaboration with the Association.
With this many people?
I guess Master's plan was to deploy Ark.
Sounds like a joke, right?
Sending the capital's best level 7
hunter to a level 3 treasure vault.
The only thing it smells of is danger.
However, Ark Brave isn't around.
What you see here are the "replacements."
You think these people can handle it?
Not sure.
Obsidian Cross has gone ahead,
but even they can't replace Ark Brave.
Only the Grievers could.
Has the White Wolf's Den's
level gone up since then?
And if it has, what's going on over there?
Huh?
What's all this?
What are all these people doing here?
Is there some kind of festival going on?
This is regarding what we
spoke about yesterday.
Oh, right. That.
Since you had requested Ark,
I tried to assemble a group that
approximates his strength.
If this isn't to your liking, I could...
Hold on... It's true that I wanted
to shove this onto Ark.
But that's because he's such a nice guy who
always gets everything done with a smile,
which means I can relax in peace.
Not to mention,
sending this many people
is gonna cost an arm and a leg.
Who's going to pay for that?
Our members are all elites,
so I think half of them should be
able to handle it with ease.
Half?! No way!
Ark was requested to handle this, right?!
What could happen at a
level 3 treasure vault?!
Everyone, please listen up.
Krai has something to say to you.
I wonder who that Krai is...
Everyone, calm yourselves.
This treasure vault was originally level 3.
You can definitely handle
it with just half of you.
Lies!
It's not a lie.
Ugh, even Tino?
Have mercy, Master.
You're starting to worry us.
Is there an irrefutable reason that you
really have to reduce our numbers?
Is there going to be a
proper reward for this?
Certainly.
Gark has acquired additional funding.
Seriously?
So we solved the money issue,
but I still haven't found Sitri's Slime...
What if it's inside the White Wolf's Den?!
Oh, well. Fine.
It's... fine?
If you guys want to do it that way,
I have no right to stop you.
If this may people go and there's nothing
there, I won't take responsibility.
Gark has words for me, I'm
going to feign ignorance so hard.
This is so stupid.
If it were me, I wouldn't even take half,
I'd go alone.
Krai's demands are always high,
but you shouldn't have
anything to complain about.
Right, Krai?
Uh, sure.
That's because you're so strong,
Stifled Shadow!
He's right!
You don't get it cuz you're tough!
Exactly!
I get why Krai is getting fed up.
This is exactly why you guys
are stuck where you are.
I know!
Krai, I'll take on this job.
With Ti.
Nope.
But why not?
Because I said no.
That would be too cruel for Tino,
plus there are already other people there.
I can picture exactly what would
happen if Liz went there.
I've decided to have everyone
here go after all.
Understood.
Then will you lead everyone in the vault?
I see! If our level 8 master
is there, it won't be so scary.
With Master's powers, those
phantoms will be a piece of cake.
Why is everyone getting hyped up?
I'm not going.
Are you stupid? Why would I go?
Hm, I think there are people
better suited to leadership,
like Sven, or...
Obsidian Cross is already there.
I have a great idea!
All right. I suppose I will go as well, then.
Wait, you're going?
However, there are some pressing
matters I cannot delay.
I will join you later.
Until then, I'll delegate
leadership to Obsidian Cross.
Understood. Everyone,
please prepare for departure.
I'm going to casually stroll in
when things are wrapping up.
What a letdown.
Sure, the level of the phantoms
has gone up...
But other than that, nothing stands out.
Let's just move on for now.
Why can't I come?!
Why? I wanna go!
Hey, please!
Please.
Please!
Calm down.
I, uh... need you to, you
know, do something else.
Oh, really?
Yes, really.
Oh, why didn't you say so earlier?
I had to do this,
or else she would just grab
Tino and run ahead.
Krai.
Should we be on the lookout for anything
in particular during this mission?
Hmm...
Oh, right!
I don't know if it'll appear,
but if you run into some sort of slime-like thing, you should be careful.
A slime?
Why would a slime appear in
the White Wolf's Den?
That's why I said I don't
know if it'll appear.
But if it does,
it's not a normal slime, so be cautious.
Got it. I'll keep that in mind.
I think this time it was
really too random...
I'm truly sorry.
Damn these hunters!
I can't believe they sent this many...
The arrogance of confronting
us mages directly.
This is the pinnacle of our research,
the mana material agitation device.
If they impede our pursuit of the truth,
our only choice is to crush them.
But we're facing Thousand Tricks.
If his party, Grieving Souls,
were to mobilize,
it'd be a real problem.
That won't be an issue.
It's true that they are one
of the capital's top parties.
But my defense system is
ready to repel them.
Besides, there are only two—no, three
of the Grieving Souls in the capital.
Thousand Tricks, Krai Andrey.
Stifled Shadow, Liz Smart.
And that vexing alchemist, Sitri Smart.
Most of them are not present?
How did you find that out?
Flick, I'm no research-obsessed fool.
I have eyes in many places where
the Akashic Tower has none.
If you have provisions against physical
attacks, dealing with Stifled Shadow is easy.
Furthermore, Thousand Tricks,
as the brain of the party,
cannot unleash his full potential without
his party members to direct.
Then the only problem is Sitri Smart.
No.
I've used numerous techniques to construct
the defense system for this facility.
It's impossible for an alchemist who
abides by the laws to overcome it.
That woman is my nemesis.
I need to do everything I can
to obliterate her completely.
Sitri has been sniffing
around this research,
based on the thesis you
left behind in the empire.
What?
The research of mana material is the essence
of the sublime ideal of the Master of Mages.
It's not something that
filthy Sitri may approach.
Master, please grant me permission
to use everything we've created
thus far to rid us of these intruders.
Very well.
Flick, and everyone else present:
Follow Sophia's orders.
Consider Sophia's words to be my words.
Understood?
Yes, sir!
All for your sublime task!
Nothing out of the ordinary here, either.
Was it perhaps overkill for us to
be dispatched for this request?
What choice did we have?
It came directly from Gark himself.
I'll trust your judgment.
However, this almost feels like
we're cleaning up the Master's mess.
Perhaps.
But you know, Henrik, one of these
days you'll also understand.
Right...
Got it. Thanks for telling me.
The situation has changed.
We'll head out for now.
Blow the whistle.
Yes, sir!
Yo, yo, Crosses.
Give me a break.
Did you seriously use the emergency signal
even though there's nothing
out of the ordinary?
Correct.
Did any of you find anything?
According to the information
the Crosses got,
we're supposed to watch out for a slime.
So, let me get this straight.
You're telling me you
trust the word of some guy
who's lazing about in the city
more than the evidence here?
That's right.
Are you shitting me?!
Listen.
We used the signal out of kindness.
The hell?
If it were the Grieving Souls instead
of us, they'd never use it.
Krai would say it's fine.
Liz or Luke have no interest
in weaker people.
Sitri would deliberately send
you ahead and study you.
But every member of our party is a healer.
It goes against our style to look
away and allow people to die.
It's not too late to resume the
investigation after our reinforcements arrive.
But if you want to die, do as you like.
But that's ridiculous!
Watch out for a slime?
Why would a trash monster
like that appear here?!
In the past, Krai once suggested we all go
out for a cherry blossom viewing.
Since it was outside the city, he told
us to bring our weapons just in case.
Cherry blossom viewing?
What are you on about?
The place we went is now a treasure vault.
Have you ever seen the moment
a treasure vault materializes?
All right, everyone. Let's begin!
It's almost as if...
Cheers!
...hell had seeped into our world.
Are you talking about... the Prism Garden?
Thousand Tricks can see the future.
The reason we spent an enormous
amount to get this Sounding Stone
was to obtain information more quickly.
Information from him is that valuable.
Hey, hey.
Krai, when are we going?
What did you have to do?
I'm ready to go.
Hey. Hey.
I'm so excited to fight in front of you.
Last time I couldn't go all out.
Right, that's true.
I did say I'd go,
and I do want to show up when the
investigation is done, but...
It's hard to know when the
right time to leave is.
Seriously?
I'm back.
What's going on?
Oh, welcome back, Sitri.
Why so soon?
Did you come back alone?
Why, though?
You're one to talk,
after you abandoned our party.
Krai, I thought you might need my skills,
so I came back.
I had a bad feeling.
Huh?
It's a powerful enemy.
We need to crush them before
they gain any more power.
Sitri Smart has finally
returned to our Krai Andrey!
The treasure vault White Wolf's
Den has inexplicably changed.
Sitri's Slime is still missing.
And the secret organization,
Akashic Tower, is moving in the shadows.
Please tune in again next time!
Um, are you really going,
Branch Manager?
Don't worry. I won't overdo it.
But you're retired.
We have the full support
of First Steps in this matter.
You should leave this to the young people.
I will not tolerate Liz making fun of me!
I can still keep up with those youngsters!
You're so immature...
Gark.
You're...
I have a favor to ask.
Akashic.
By: Noctus and Disciples feat. Sophia
A!
All for the pursuit! Akashic Tower!
Akashic.
Ka!
Calling on you to prepare
yourself! Akashic Tower!
Akashic.
Shic!
Shic shank mages, for our mentor!
Shic shank...?
Next time, on Let This Grieving Soul...
...Retire!
Submit to us, Thousand Tricks!
Episode 07
The Akashic Tower Wants to Experiment
"The Akashic Tower Wants to Experiment."